A Finding Aid to the Beatrice Fenton Papers, 1836-1984, bulk 1890-1978, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fentbeat
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, 1890-1978; Series 10; 1 Linear feet Boxes 9-10, MGP 6
  - Artwork, 1912-1915; 10.3
    - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Two photographs of Peter Moran's Portrait Bust and four photographs of Seaweed Fountain.
    - Glass Plate Negative, 1 Glass negatives (Box MGP 6)
  - Albums, 1909-1910; 10.4
    - Photograph Album 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Photograph Album 2 (Travel Photographs), 1909-1910 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Photograph Album 3 (Travel Photographs), 1909-1910 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous Travel Photographs, 1909-1910 (Box 9, Folder 72)